// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [{
        numb: 1,
        question: "Give the full meaning of DNA ?",
        answer: "Deoxyribonucleic Acid",
        options: [
            "Acid deoxide",
            "Deribonucleic Acid",
            "Deoxyribonucleic Acid",
            "Deamine Acid"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Which Classification level has most organisms ?",
        answer: "Kingdom",
        options: [
            "Phylum",
            "Kingdom",
            "Class",
            "Phyla"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "The cell structure responsible for regulating passage in and out of a cell ?",
        answer: "Cell membrane",
        options: [
            "Cell wall",
            "Cytoplasm",
            "Golgi body",
            "Cell membrane"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "The biological classification of plants and animals ?",
        answer: "Taxonomy",
        options: [
            "Taxonomy",
            "Dermatology",
            "Anthropology",
            "Nomenclature"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "What is the scientific name of man ?",
        answer: "Homo sapien",
        options: [
            "Homo sapien",
            "Agama agama",
            "Galus galus",
            "Homo erectus"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "What cell structure is not present only in animal cells ?",
        answer: "Cell wall",
        options: [
            "Cell membrane",
            "Vacuole",
            "Mitochondrion",
            "Cell wall"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Two main blood cells found in humans ?",
        answer: "Red blood cells and White blood cells",
        options: [
            "White blood cells and Platelets",
            "Red blood cells and White blood cells",
            "Reb blood cells and cellulase",
            "Platelets and Red blood cells"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "What immunity is gotten right from the birth of a child?",
        answer: "Passive immunity",
        options: [
            "Passive immunity",
            "Active immunity",
            "Both passive and active immunities",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Which of the below is not a Blood group type ?",
        answer: "F",
        options: [
            "A",
            "B",
            "F",
            "AB"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "What is the full meaning of AIDS ?",
        answer: "Acquired immune deficiency syndrome",
        options: [
            "Acquired immune deficient syndrome",
            "Acquired immune deficiency sign",
            "Acquired immune deficit syndrome",
            "Acquired immune deficiency syndrome"
        ]
    },
];